There's been some breaking news right now.
Why don't we start things off
with this red headline that's crossed.
And he was postal service mail,
the curbs, the mail ballot curbs.
Okay, one concept there
has been blocked by a judge
for now, not a ton of
details on this just yet,
but that's so far the
information that we have.
We will bring you more
as we get more context
on this, but for now,
that's off the table.
- Yeah, it seems like
this judge is weighing
a long-term block ahead
of the US midterms as well,
so the timing of that is quite
interesting too as we count down.
Yeah, so temporarily
blocked by a judge here today.
Let's switch gears and talk a bit more
about what's been going on, right, Bitcoin?
I mean, what a quarter, whatever you found
that we're seeing, we're back to 80,000.
You got to think maybe
this whole debasement trade
has come back in a
big way, that's maybe
fueling this, but yeah,
what else is going on?
We got a big conference in Hong
Kong that's wrapping up today as well.
- Yes, the very creatively named Bitcoin
Asia Conference, starts today in Hong Kong.
Well, simple is better,
gets the message through.
One of the company's
attending holds one of the largest
Bitcoin Treasuries among
publicly traded firms.
You can see, of course,
company stock trading.
On your screens right now,
tracking, as we were just
pointing out, there of
course, the price in Bitcoin,
maybe you can think,
Scott Bessent and the angst
in the landing of the bond market debasement
trade, and everything in between here,
for now at where 80 grand
right now on Bitcoin itself.
Joining us now exclusively here
on set is the CEO Rafael Segeri.
Thank you for coming in
and very nice to see you.
- Thank you, my pleasure to be here.
- A few weeks into the job.
- Yes.
- How's that been?
Do you have enough information
right now to answer that question?
- So far so good.
I've been at the board of the company for
a while, so I know the company really well.
I've been a Bitcoiner
for longer than a decade,
so this is all in what I've been
doing, so it's nothing of that is new.
- It's an interesting time for the company.
In the news, of course,
there have been some
deals that perhaps don't
seem to be happening.
I understand, of course,
there could be other plays
that, well, give us an
understanding of where things stand.
- Yeah, I think the important thing to
know is that the way that we're looking
to build a treasury company is slightly
different than what we've seen before.
We're looking to build a
Bitcoin operating business,
so what we're gonna be
looking at are profitable
cash flow companies to
bring into our balance sheet.
Similar to how Berkshire had way
forward about building their business,
we're gonna be looking to do
the same thing for Bitcoin, right?
And the one of the deals we're looking at
is a company I founded,
which is electron energy.
It's a mining company, a
Bitcoin mining company.
That grew to be one of the
largest mining companies
in the world, and we're thinking about
that that deal has been announced.
It's in the process, it
hasn't been confirmed yet,
but that's a good example
of companies that we're
gonna be looking for to
add that the 21 balance sheet.
Other than that,
election, we're gonna be
looking at other companies
should bring as well.
I mean, A, it's gonna be a
core focus of what we do.
That's one of the advantages
of being a Bitcoin bear market
is that there are more
opportunities for us to look at.
It's exactly good teams,
cheap assets, right?
It's the right time to build.
- Yeah, it's interesting.
The Berkshire Happy Model, right?
Where Bitcoin is sort
of the balance sheet,
right, at the center,
and then you're kind of
operating around the
business and built around it.
Tell us a bit more about just what
21 capital is gonna look like, right?
Is it more about a digital asset treasury,
or are you gonna be more
about financial services?
Like how do you chart
the next path forward?
- Yeah, it's a good question.
It's, as I mentioned,
I think the first thing
is to operating companies,
so that's the first pillar.
The second pillar, which
is an important pillar,
is capital markets,
which similar to what
other trajectories
companies have been doing,
we're gonna be looking to raise actually
that, everything that they do traditionally,
but the important thing is
that when you have operating
companies, it opens the doors to do much
more in terms of financing, we can look
into securitizing revenues, we can look
into issuing different kinds of that, right?
Instead of just being something
that is backed by Bitcoin,
it can be backed by collateral of
revenues of the companies, right?
So that makes it much different.
And then on top of that,
I think the other thing
that is gonna happen with
Bitcoin is that you're gonna have
an expanding credit market around Bitcoin,
landing against Bitcoin is already growing,
and I think it's in the future, it's gonna
continue to be a good business to build,
and the way to think about
it, is that we're building
a different kind of financial services
industry on top of Bitcoin, right?
But going to the
commodity with a collateral,
but also very good basis for
building a financial system around it.
- And the currency you're using,
or you'll be looking to use for these M&A
transactions, would it mainly be Bitcoin?
Are you using something else?
Maybe just to also ask, how many
Bitcoin do you actually are you sitting on?
- So we have 43,513
bitcoins in our balance sheets.
So roughly a little bit more
than $3 billion at today's value.
- Okay, and the currency at which you will
be conducting most of the M&A, are you?
- It will depend on the transaction.
What we can say is
that our stock is trained
at the discount through
an AV right now, right?
So probably it wouldn't
make sense should we should
stock at an AV, should
we eliminate transactions?
But the good thing about
doing some of these business
with profitable companies that these some
of these deals may be self-funding, right?
And that's how we made it
looking at doing with that,
with other activities, or
maybe even using our Bitcoin
as collateral, right now
we have around two-thirds
of our balance sheet
that it's unencumbered,
that we could use as
collateral to get some leverage.
So there are different
things that we could do,
potentially should do
the acquisitions, right?
- And tell us a little bit
about the businesses.
What's the first operating
visit you're looking at
that could generate a
positive cash flow for you guys?
- The very interesting about the time
that we're in Bitcoin right
now is that what we're building
now I've been thinking
about something like
this for a long time and
you can only do it now
because Bitcoin is at a
place of institutionalization
that we haven't
seen before, right?
So the business can, the
business that we're looking for
is not only business that are
profitable cash flow positive
but that can scale
with more capital, right?
Up until a few years ago was
very hard to find businesses
that could scale because the total of
the taxable market was smaller, right?
Bitcoin was still growing
in terms of adoption.
I think with last year,
you know, a few years ago
if the ETF's coming in,
more institutions coming in,
as I said, I worked my
whole career in Wall Street
and I worked at Goldman
Deutsche, big companies, right?
And you couldn't even,
up until a few years ago,
I couldn't even have a
conversation about Bitcoin
with some of my
colleagues because they rock,
they wouldn't even hear
about what you were saying
and that switched completely
from where we were before.
Now I have actually the opposite.
A lot of them reaching out to me and say,
"Well, we're thinking about adding Bitcoin
"through client's portfolio,
show our own balance sheet.
"We're doing transactions with Bitcoin.
"We're looking at trades
using Bitcoin as collateral.
"That wasn't thinkable
maybe a couple of years ago.
" And that gets, as I
think, where we are in 21,
I think this is the perfect
time to be building.
When you look at the
combination of the bear market,
which maybe coming to
an end, who knows, right,
with Bitcoin at 80,000, and
then the opportunities ahead
and where Bitcoin is, I think this is the
perfect time to be doing what we're doing.
- And what's the framework you're using
to look at which types of companies to buy
and as investors of 21, am I
buying a holding company?
The same buying Berkshire, for example,
and are you going to be accruing dividends?
How is that poll?
- Yeah, good question.
And so Bitcoin is our benchmark
at the end of the day, right?
So every investment that we look at
is gonna be measured against Bitcoin.
If we can't be Bitcoin,
then it's much easier for our
shareholders to just go out
and buy Bitcoin as an asset, right?
They can buy it through an
ETF, through direct custody, right?
So what we're looking
through is have better risk
adjusted returns, and it's
just not beating Bitcoin.
It's having better risk adjusted
returns compared to Bitcoin, right?
That should be the
benchmark that will guide
every single one of
our decisions going on.
- What is that hurdle now, I'm curious.
- Well, it depends, right?
That's the hard thing about Bitcoin is that
it's still in discovery process, right?
It's a drop of the bucket
in ocean of liquidity, right?
Look at Bitcoin, one
and a half trillion dollars
in terms of market gap,
compared to gold at
30 billion, real estate
at 300 plus, right?
So if you look at where Bitcoin is in
terms of potential for saving technology,
'cause ultimately I think Bitcoin is the
best savings technology of the world,
and it's gonna capture some of the
monetary premium of these assets, right?
I think if you look long term, Bitcoin
has a lot of upside potential short term.
If you measure it, try to
measure what the benchmark is.
It could be anything.
Try some of the short term can move anyway,
because again, it's still
an asset in discovery, right?
- I mean, we're seeing
a bit of recovery, 80,000.
What do you think is driving that?
- I think first of all, it was, the price
was very depressed for a long time.
We've seen that if you've
been in Bitcoin for a while, right?
Again, because it's still an asset,
the kind of interest
that your seagulls up and
down with time, and
we were just at a period
that a lot of the interest
that was driven by
the ETFs, everything that
we mentioned last year,
dried down a little bit,
and now it's coming back.
So I think it's just, it
was like a spring that
was coiled and it's
kind of like coming out.
But as I said before,
it's still a drop in
the bucket on the
ocean of liquidity, right?
And on top of that, I think the
recent macro events help Bitcoin.
Bitcoin is a monetary asset
that different than anything else
that we've ever seen as
humans, it's extremely predictable.
The monetary issue is written in code.
You don't have 12 different
federal reserve banks making
determinations, or opaque, that you
don't know what's going to happen.
Treasury chairs coming in and
trying to buy the long end of the curve.
Nothing of that happens, right?
It's extremely predictable.
You know that every 10
minutes and you block on average,
every 10 minutes and you
block is going to come in.
3N18, Bitcoin is going to be issued, right?
You know that every four years that habs,
it's all written in code,
it's all transparent,
it's all open source, and
we've never seen this.
And going back to Berchard,
Charlie Munger actually
used to say that predictability
should trade at the premium, right?
And I think Bitcoin should
trade at the premium
exactly because the monetary
policy, it's exactly-- it's a line.
You know exactly what it's going to
be, you know, for the foreseeable future.
And unfortunately, we live in a
world with a lot of uncertainty, right?
So now not only politically,
but on the monetary side as well.
And I think that's what
we're seeing on Bitcoin, right?
Now it's a lot of like
the realization that this is
a very different asset from
what we've seen before.
And you mentioned earlier at the start,
you've been a Bitcoiner for a long time.
Do we have a better
understanding now what kind of asset
it is based on how it
behaves in the whole relation?
How has that changed
over the years up until this
point where it's been
stable largely this year?
So David, I'll tell you, I
think that Grocking Bitcoin
is very hard because Bitcoin
is multidisciplinary, right?
I was very lucky or unlucky, depending how
you want to see that I grew up in Brazil.
And, you know, I went my teenage years
in the 90s in Brazil, late 80s, early 90s.
When inflation was wild,
like we would have money,
literally losing its
value overnight, right?
I remember my mother giving
me money to school for lunch
and say, here's the money, don't bring
it back because if you spend everything,
because if you bring it back, it's
going to be worthless by a few days.
So it's kind of like
ingrained on my mind
that money can lose
value a long time, right?
And on top of that, so that's the social
aspect, you have the technological aspect,
which is, you know,
Bitcoin is stitched though,
it's globally native, it can
be moved anywhere, right?
As I was saying, it's all written
in code, it's easy to understand.
And I think it takes
time for people to really
understand all of the
different aspects of Bitcoin.
But what I can tell is I said, gradually,
we're starting to see more
and more of the institutional side
of the world coming
in, understanding Bitcoin
and adopting Bitcoin
as a reserve asset.
- Half-ail, thank you so much.
- Yeah, sure, let's do this again.
- Thank you so much.
- Next time you're in town.
Half-ail Zaguri, there's CEO at 21.
Capital, we'll leave you again
with a look at markets, right?
And that's quite their
cross-attack when you market.
I think lastly, check we were
flat and largely still are across.
The Hanks and Tech index at least,
Hospital is down, Nicky is... let's call it
mixed, across the Asia Pacific equator.